The only reason anybody would be against reparations is if they don't feel that this country has
anything to repair in how it has treated and continues to treat black folks. I don't think
reparations for something that happened 150 years ago for whom none of us currently living or
responsible is a good idea. First off, Mitch, you were alive 100 years ago. Look at you. Second,
reparations are not just about slavery. They're about repairing the incessant harm that has been
done to black people in this country since we were stolen and brought here and that does not
end with slavery. These people act like Jim Crow was just like a minor inconvenience. It was
violence! And I don't know if y'all been looking around lately but basically reparations should be
owed for what was done like 15 minutes ago in this country. We've you know tried to deal with our
original sin of slavery by fighting a civil war. If the civil war was really about righting the wrongs
of slavery then we wouldn't have all these confederate flags and confederate statues still
just confederating around to this day. To this day! By passing landmark civil rights legislation.
These people wake up every morning to undo civil rights legislation.
We've elected an African-American president. Now you know you ain't vote for Barack.
We need to become reparationists. We need to make preparations for reparations. And I say that comes
with us first making reparations a part of our culture. This should be a part of our lifestyle and
we should be demanding that reparations be given to us by whoever is in the presidency and by whoever
wants to be president. And also by our local and state governments. And I don't think that means just
waiting to the last minute of an election and saying that we're not going to vote for you unless you give
us reparations. Nah. We should be getting behind candidates who already believe in this. And all you
white folks who want to be down? Maybe you better be reparationists too. That's the new question for
your white friends. Do you believe black people should get reparations? See reparations are not a capital
game. They're an ethical practice. Because in a society where advancement is determined by money, the only
way to correct the systematic hindrance of that advancement is by providing money. Reparations are not some
far-reaching thing that have never been figured out before. We need to stop looking at reparations as
something we need to imagine. Consider them as something that is very real that needs to happen. What we need to
imagine is what we are going to do with the reparations to make sure that our community and
ourselves are taken care of. We need to become reparationists.